<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Energy | 陈斌彬的技术博客]]></title>
  <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/categories/energy/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2016-08-23T10:12:51+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://cnbin.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[陈斌彬]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sports]]></title>
    <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/19/sports/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-19T09:45:16+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/19/sports</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!--More-->


<p>Sport plays an important role in our daily life.Most of us begin our day with some kind of exercise or sport.Athletics is part of our university curriculum.Many students play on either the departmental or university sports team after a hard day of class.</p>

<p>运动在日常生活中起着重要作用。我们大多数人在新的一天开始时总要做一些运动。体育课是我们大学课程的一部分。许多学生在一天的紧张学习之后还参加了系或学校的运动队。</p>

<p>Some people take sports far too seriously.Some people are only interested in how their favourite sports team does: they don&rsquo;t care much about their country or the rest of the world.These people often get into fights if their team loses.</p>

<p>有些人对运动过分认真。有些人只对他们喜欢的运动队的输赢感兴趣，他们对他们的国家或世界其它地方的情况不太关心。这些人在他们所关心的运动队输了时往往打斗起来。</p>

<p>When I have time for sports there is one that I like more than any other.I find bas ketball both a physical and a mental challenge.Runing, jumping, and shooting, are also enjoyable and healthful sports.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends]]></title>
    <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/12/friends/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-12T09:44:14+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/12/friends</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!--More-->


<p>Friends are very important to us.When in trouble, we need friends to offer us en couragement and help. With success achieved, we also need friends to share our joys.It＇s hard to imagine life without friendship!</p>

<p>朋友对我们非常重要。当遇到困难时，我们需要朋友给予鼓励和帮助：获得了成功，我们也需要朋友分享我们的欢乐。没有友谊的生活是难以想象的!</p>

<p>A person should make as many friends as he can.The more friends he has, the more meaningful his life will be.Similarly, a country, too, needs friends.China today, for example, has friends all over the world.With the open policy being successfully carried out, she is certain to make more friends in the future.</p>

<p>一个人应广交朋友。朋友越多，他的生活将更有意义。同样，一个国家也需要朋友。譬如，今天的中国，朋友遍天下。随着开放政策成功的施行，中国将会有更多的朋友。</p>

<p>However,real friends are not easy to find.That＇s why we highly value our friend ship with them.False friends also exist. They may have a bad influence on our character and are even worse open enemies.Therefore, it is essential we take care in making friends.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Become an Interesting Person]]></title>
    <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/05/become-an-interesting-person/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-05T16:05:12+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/09/05/become-an-interesting-person</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!--More-->


<p>In my life,I regard everyday as New Year.Yeah,it&rsquo;s a wonderful idea.May be you can have a try.</p>

<p>I think,what&rsquo;s meaning of people to work hard everyday?</p>

<p>For money? For house? For avoid poor? Or for not boring?</p>

<p>I feel many people earned more money,they become more unhappy.</p>

<p>Why? I don&rsquo;t understand too. Because I am a oridinary person.</p>

<p>I like to do the real self,to do something interesting.</p>

<p>Playing joke,wathching comedy,singing happy songs.Yeah,try more different things,and then I fell more positive energy in my heart.</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s amazing!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sit in Silence]]></title>
    <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/08/29/sit-in-silence/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-29T11:49:33+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/08/29/sit-in-silence</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!--More-->


<p>In this symposium, better is it to only sit in silence. To express one's feelings as the end draws near is too intimate a task. That I would mention only one thought that comes to me as a listenerin: the riders in a race do not stop short when they reach the goal, there is a little finishing canter before coming to a standstill, there is time to hear the kind voice of friends, and to say to oneself, the work is done. But just as one says that, the answer comes, the race is over, but the work never is done while the power to work remains. The canter that brings you to a standstill need not be only coming to rest; it cannot be while you still live. But to live is to function, that is all there is in living. So I end with a land from a Latin voice: death, death, clutches my ear, and says, live, I am coming.&ndash;By Oliver Wendell Holmes </p>

<p>译文： 此刻，沉默是金。要在生命即将完结之时表达个人感受并非易事。但我只是想谈谈作为一名倾听者的看法。骑士们并非一到终点就立刻止步。他们继续缓步向前，倾听朋友们的欢呼。他们虽然告诉自己行程已经结束了。正如人们所说结果出来了,比赛结束了。但只要动力仍在，人生之旅就尚未结束。终点之后的慢跑并非停止不前，因为活着便不能如此。活着就要有所作为，这才是生命的真谛。最后谨以一句古拉丁格言与各位共勉：死神不止，奋斗不止。
 
&ndash;[美]奥利佛·文德尔·荷默斯 </p>

<p>in this symposium:此刻  </p>

<p>At this timegoal: n.目的,目标 </p>

<p>standstill: n.停止 </p>

<p>The grandest of these ideals is an unfolding American promise that everyone belongs, that everyone deserves a chance that no insignificant person was ever born. Americans are called to enact this promise in our lives and in our laws. And though our nation has sometimes halted, and sometimes delayed, we must follow no other course. Through much of the last century, America's faith in freedom and democracy was a rock in a raging sea. Now it is a seed upon the wind, taking root in many nations. Our democratic faith is more than the creed of our country, it is the inborn hope of our humanity, an ideal we carry but do not own, a trust we bear and pass along. And even after nearly 225 years, we have a long way yet to travel. &ndash;By George W.Bush </p>

<p>译文： 这些理想中最伟大的是正在慢慢实现的美国的承诺，这就是：每个人都有自身的价值，每个人都有成功的机会，每个人天生都会有所作为的。美国人民肩负着一种使命，那就是要竭力将这个诺言变成生活中和法律上的现实。虽然我们的国家过去在追求实现这个承诺的途中停滞不前甚至倒退，但我们仍将坚定不移地完成这一使命。在上个世纪的大部分时间里，美国自由民主的信念犹如汹涌大海中的岩石。现在它更像风中的种子，把自由带给每个民族。在我们的国家，民主不仅仅是一种信念，而是全人类的希望；民主，我们不会独占，而会竭力让大家分享；民主，我们将铭记于心并且不断传播。225年过去了，我们仍有很长的路要走。 
&ndash;[美]乔治·布什 </p>

<p>insignificant: adj.无关紧要的、可忽略的 </p>

<p>democracy: n.民主政治、民主主</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Can Do for Your Country]]></title>
    <link href="http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/08/22/what-can-do-for-your-country/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-22T11:47:45+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://cnbin.github.io/blog/2015/08/22/what-can-do-for-your-country</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<!--More-->


<p>My fellow Americans, ask not what your country can do for you, ask what you can do for your country. My fellow citizens of the world, ask not what America will do for you, but what together we can do for the freedom of men. Finally whether you are citizens of America, or citizens of the world, ask of us here, the same high standards of strength and sacrifice which we ask of you. With a good conscience of our only sure reward, with history the final judge of our deeds, let us go forth to lead the land we love, asking His blessing and His help, but knowing that here on earth, God&rsquo;s work must truly be our own.&ndash;By John F. Kennedy</p>

<p>美国同胞们，不要问美国能为你们做些什么，应该问你们能为美国贡献些什么。全世界的同胞们，不要
问美国将为你做些什么，应该问我们一同能为人类的自由做些什么。最后，无论你是美国公民还是其他国家的同胞，你们应该要求我们献出我们同样要求于你们的高度的力量和牺牲。无愧于心是我们惟一可靠的奖赏，历史是我们行动最终的裁判。这一切让我们大步向前，去引领我们所热爱的这片土地。我们祈求上帝的保佑和帮助，但我们很清楚，上帝在尘世的工作必定是我们自己的工作。</p>

<p>&ndash;[美]约翰·肯尼迪</p>

<p>citizen: n.市民,公民</p>

<p>sacrifice: n./ v.牺牲,献身</p>

<p>conscience: n.良心,道德心</p>

<p>Let me express my firm belief that the only thing we have to fear is fear itself-nameless, unreasoning, unjustified terror, which paralyzes needed efforts to convert retreat into advance. In every dark hour of our national life, a leadership of frankness and vigor has met with that understanding and support of the people themselves, which is essential to victory and I am convinced that you will again give that support to leadership in these critical days. In such a spirit on my part and on yours, we face our common difficulties. They concern, thank God, only material things.&ndash;By Franklin D. Roosevelt</p>

<p>译文 让我来表明我坚定的信念：我们不得不害怕的其实就是害怕本身&ndash;一种莫名奇妙的、丧失理智的、毫无根据的恐惧。它把人们转退为进所需要的种种努力化为泡影。但凡在我国生活阴云密布的时刻，坦率而有活力的领导都得到过人民的理解和支持，从而为胜利准备了不可缺少的必要条件。我相信，在目前危机的时刻，大家会再次给与同样的支持。我和你们都要以这种精神来共同面对困难。感谢上帝，这些困难只是物质方面的。</p>

<p> &ndash;[美]弗兰克林·罗斯福</p>

<p> unreasoning: adj.丧失理智的</p>

<p> unjustified: adj.毫无根据的</p>

<p> frankness: n.率直,坦白</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
